♪ Holding me back ♪
♪ Gravity’s holding me back ♪
♪ I want you to hold out the
palm of your hand ♪
♪ Why don’t we leave it at
that? ♪
♪ Nothing to say ♪
♪ When everything gets in the
way ♪
♪ Seems you cannot be replace ♪
♪ And I’m the one who will
stay ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ In this world ♪
♪ It’s just us ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same as
it was ♪
♪ In this world ♪
♪ It’s just us ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same as
it was ♪
♪ As it was ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same ♪
♪ Answer the phone ♪
♪ “Harry, you’re no good alone ♪
♪ Why are you sitting at home on
the floor? ♪
♪ "What kind of pills are you
on?" ♪
♪ Ringing the bell ♪
♪ And nobody’s coming to help ♪
♪ Your daddy lives by himself ♪
♪ He just wants to know that
you’re well ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ In this world ♪
♪ It’s just us ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same as
it was ♪
♪ In this world ♪
♪ It’s just us ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same as
it was ♪
♪ As it was ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same ♪
♪ Go home ♪
♪ Get ahead ♪
♪ Light speed internet ♪
♪ I don’t want to talk about the
way that it was ♪
♪ Leave America ♪
♪ Two kids follow her ♪
♪ I don’t want to talk about
who’s doing it first ♪
♪ (Hey!) ♪
♪ As it was ♪
♪ You know it’s not the same as
it was ♪
♪ As it was ♪